{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Liquid or Spray-On Siding Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46330/":{"taskOID":46330,"originalTaskOID":46330,"setID":1015,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":200142,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of surface do you want to cover with liquid siding?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3760,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Masonry (brick/stone)","answerDisplayText":"Masonry (brick/stone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7089,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood siding","answerDisplayText":"Wood siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1556,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete block","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":773,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":857,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Asbestos shingles","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos shingles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200143,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Interest","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why are you interested in liquid siding? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17240,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Weatherproofing","answerDisplayText":"Weatherproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17241,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fill \u0026 repair cracks","answerDisplayText":"Fill \u0026 repair cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17242,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Prevent fading","answerDisplayText":"Prevent fading","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17243,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ease of maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Ease of maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17244,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reduce frequency of painting","answerDisplayText":"Reduce frequency of painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17245,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Environmentally safe","answerDisplayText":"Environmentally safe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200145,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6558,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two story","answerDisplayText":"Two story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":200142,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of surface do you want to cover with liquid siding?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3760,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Masonry (brick/stone)","answerDisplayText":"Masonry (brick/stone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7089,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood siding","answerDisplayText":"Wood siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1556,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete block","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":773,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":857,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Asbestos shingles","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos shingles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3760,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Masonry (brick/stone)","answerDisplayText":"Masonry (brick/stone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7089,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood siding","answerDisplayText":"Wood siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1556,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete block","answerDisplayText":"Concrete block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":773,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":857,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Asbestos shingles","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos shingles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200143,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Interest","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why are you interested in liquid siding? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17240,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Weatherproofing","answerDisplayText":"Weatherproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17241,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fill \u0026 repair cracks","answerDisplayText":"Fill \u0026 repair cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17242,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Prevent fading","answerDisplayText":"Prevent fading","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17243,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ease of maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Ease of maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17244,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reduce frequency of painting","answerDisplayText":"Reduce frequency of painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17245,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Environmentally safe","answerDisplayText":"Environmentally safe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17240,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Weatherproofing","answerDisplayText":"Weatherproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17241,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fill \u0026 repair cracks","answerDisplayText":"Fill \u0026 repair cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17242,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Prevent fading","answerDisplayText":"Prevent fading","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17243,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ease of maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Ease of maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17244,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reduce frequency of painting","answerDisplayText":"Reduce frequency of painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17245,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Environmentally safe","answerDisplayText":"Environmentally safe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200145,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6558,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two story","answerDisplayText":"Two story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6558,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two story","answerDisplayText":"Two story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46330/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46330,"taskName":"Liquid (Spray-On) Siding - Apply","taskDescription":"Apply Liquid (Spray-On) Siding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Liquid or Spray-On Siding Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5215,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Liquid application stone spray sparyon","textMessagingName":"Liquid Siding","rolloverLongDesc":null,"rolloverShortDesc":"Exterior coating for protecting \u0026 beautifying surfaces","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply Liquid (Spray-On) Siding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Apply Spray-On Siding \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Liquid Siding Application","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":69,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Spray-on Siding Apply","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Liquid (Spray-On) Siding - Apply","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Liquid Siding Project","urlName":"Liquid-Spray-On-Siding-Apply","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Liquid or Spray-On Siding Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Liquid,application,stone,spray,sparyon,world,material,maintenance,roofing,exterior,concrete,Spray-On,Siding,Apply","emcCategoryOid":-12064,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1015,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}